<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Autodidact Engineer on Autodidact Engineer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Autodidact Engineer on Autodidact Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:17:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A URL Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/a-url-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/a-url-journey/</guid>
      <description>I was recently asked, &amp;ldquo;What happens when you type a URL into your browser?&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a question that always makes me pause, trying to gauge the right level of detail. This time, I clearly missed the mark. In hindsight, I should have asked some clarifying questions to better understand the depth of knowledge the person was seeking. It&amp;rsquo;s a lesson I know well, but sometimes, in the heat of the moment, even the simplest things can trip us up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To the kube and back again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/minikube-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/minikube-intro/</guid>
      <description>My Minikube journey began with a spark of curiosity ignited by the book kubernetes Up &amp;amp; Running. Minikube was popping up everywhere—articles, tech talks, the whole shebang—but I was still a newbie.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;d just built my own little lab with a trusty old Dell Poweredge R710, and I was itching to dive headfirst into the Kubernetes world and see what all the buzz was about! Fast forward to today, and I&amp;rsquo;m proud to say I&amp;rsquo;m contributing to both the Kubernetes and Minikube projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m Sylvester, a tech enthusiast with a lifelong passion for building innovative solutions. My career journey has taken me from the fast-paced world of finance to the forefront of artificial intelligence, with a growing interest in contributing to the Kubernetes open-source project. I&amp;rsquo;m driven by a relentless curiosity and a desire to harness the power of technology to make a positive impact.&#xA;My Tech Adventures: From Wall Street to Open Source: I&amp;rsquo;ve honed my skills building complex trading and settlement systems, but my heart now belongs to the limitless possibilities of AI and the power of cloud-native technologies like Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
